Equal Love Costume Edition 10 Edition Decided!
Special Talk Live!
Yay!
And what a special guest we have today!
Please come in!
I am Shinobu Chino. I'm Shinobu Chino, and it's nice to meet you.
We have Shinobu Chino, who has been working on the costumes for Equal Love, here today.
Thank you very much.
Let's have fun.
Mr. Shinobu Chino is a director and designer of Osae Company.
It's the first time, isn't it?
Together with you.
I thought so.
I thought we were together.
That's for sure.
So, now, everyone, Group 10.
I'm in group 10.
It's the same as Chan-han.
Chan-han.
How are you doing? Maika.
I am very happy.
So many people came.
Yes.
It means that your fans picked up the book, right?
I'm glad to hear that.
It's a great book.
I really hope many people see it.
I want people who are not fans to look at it.
Fans.
Maika's pressure.
Now, let's start with the special talk live.
Tell us! Shinobu-san.
The members will ask Shinobu-san questions about her costumes, her work, and even her private life.
We asked them to write their questions on the card. Ladies and gentlemen.
Okay, let's start with the first one.
What is the outfit that Shinobu-san calls "THE equal love"?
Who is the member who wrote this?
Yes, it was me.
I think the most important thing about Equal Love is that it is "garish" in my opinion.
What is "girlish"?
Girlish is one of them.
And delicate. Everyone has a sensitive side, and I think that is what makes Equal Love what it is,
That's why I always try to add detailed decorations to the costumes and sounds.
That's for sure.
When you see the fans up close..,
What?
It's so detailed!
It's like small and big.
It's fine.
The first thing I thought was, "I'm getting a feel for Equal Love.
I thought I got one of them.
First there was the wong-choo-wong-choo.
And then
I thought I got a sense of the style of Equal Love.
I thought, "This is what it feels like.
It's a little bit
There's also an air of ennui
I have Equal Love, so...
It's not cheerful.
Everyone...
I think I got the ambience of ennui
I think I've expressed the ennui very well.
That's what I'm trying to say.
I think those two lines
I feel like we're running on those two lines.
I guess that's what our image is.
I had a chance to shoot a YouTube video with Ms. Yukirin the other day.
I got a pretty good impression of us at that time, too.
Shy and quiet.
But recently we've changed our greeting so that the staff doesn't think we're shy.
That's right!
The greeting I used to give was...
I'm Equal Dove, and it's nice to meet you.
Pleased to meet you.
I used to be quite serious.
But then I saw other idol groups...
We are Equal Dub, and it's nice to meet you.
Not much has changed
Not much has changed.
Okay, let's continue.
How do you decide on the different types of costumes to make?
I'm curious.
Who is this?
That's me.
How do you decide who's going to show their shoulders and who's going to have their shoulders bare?
How do you decide who gets the shoulders and who gets the body?
I guess that's it.
I'm very conscious of everyone's frame and character.
Especially when it comes to collaborations.
Each of them has their own character.
There are totally different types of residents.
So I wanted to make sure that each of them stood out from the others.
Keara is always happy to do this.
I'm quite happy with it.
I do a lot of clicky designs, like clicky designs.
But when I did that in the beginning, people would ask me if I was okay with it.
You guys don't have a lot of confidence.
I don't think so.
That's why I think I scored 100 today at the fitting. Like...
I want you to think that I look the best in this outfit.
So, basically, I try to make variations.
I really think about each person when I design.
I have a variation of this pattern that I would like to show to the public someday.
I'd like to show it to the public someday.
I'd like to take a look at it.
If people buy a lot of them, we'll release it.
Please reprint it again.
I'll see you then.
That's when.
Next, do you have any rejected costumes?
Rejected costumes?
Of course.
I thought that might be the case.
I don't think it was rejected in its entirety.
Sacha did a great job of communicating with us.
That's important.
I mean, I know the details of what you want to do.
I know a little bit about what you want to do.
We're talking about the 7th anniversary after the 6th anniversary.
Early.
They want to do this for the next hate.
Isn't that too soon?
It's too soon.
I'm looking forward to it.
That's why I've already decided.
You're early.
Impatient
Until a year from now
Go on
Go on.
What's with the outfit, outfit, outfit?
It's a pun.
What?
I don't know if I like this one. Who's this?
Who's this?
I looked at it like crazy.
I looked at it so much.
What?
It just popped into my head. I must have been thinking about the wrong thing.
Wait a minute.
I'm pretty sure he's blushing.
Who's that?
And it's directed at me.
Who wrote this? It even says "who wrote this?
Yes, it's written. It's written.
I'll write it down. I just wanted you to know.
What is it? This.
I'm sorry.
It just popped into my head. I was being playful.
The comment section is a mess.
It's getting hotter and hotter.
It's so fast.
It's so fast!
Follow me.
The Piccola Club will one day stand in the Tokyo Dome.
What do you think they'll be wearing?
Wait a minute.
Let's see...
When Piccola Club stands in Tokyo Dome someday...
What kind of costume do you think they'll wear?
Excuse me.
Yes, sir.
Who is this?
Yes, that's me.
Grandma.
One day I'll be in a bigger venue, even bigger.
I'll be standing in an even bigger venue.
What kind of costumes will the Picola Club wear?
We have one idea.
I'm not sure if we should do it.
There are three things I want us to do.
Three things.
First, for the production.
We all levitate.
No, no, no.
I'd like to have someone from the Negotiator's Council.
But we're not.
I'm already flying for Montorm.
I want to. I want to.
I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it.
Wow.
I really want to do it.
And... and...
It's like a float.
It's like a really sparkly carriage.
Wow.
I want to do that.
I definitely want to do that.
I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it
I want to spread the song
The other thing I really want to do is...
I want to make it so that everyone is a princess.
Real princess dresses.
What?
Dresses?
Dresses.
I love this one, too.
I'm gonna buy this one really fast.
Oh.
Another one.
It's too gorgeous.
Gorgeous!
If it's 10 people in a dome, I can do it.
We can do it.
Yeah?
I'll do my best.
Please do.
Um...
Please.
Ume...
Let's move on to the next project.
Shinobu-san, please give the title call.
Yes, please.
squeak squeak squeak squeak
A little more...
A little more.
Almost...
I'm dying of love!
Love Equals Love Crush Collection
Yay
Crush Collection
Let's see...
Shinobu-san will die of a crush
Shinobu-san has chosen this combination of the members and their outfits
Shinobu-san chose this combination of members and outfits for us!
Thank you so much!
That's great!
So, here we go...
Please put up one by one the members and their outfits that make you
Please put them up one by one!
Yes, please!
Please put up these costumes one by one.
Thank you very much.
What do you think?
Right away.
Already.
Ten, fifteen minutes.
Very fast.
Very fast
Extremely fast
If we were doing it, how many hours would this take?
Maybe one more.
Not even close.
Not at all.
It's gonna take forever.
I'll get right to it.
Let's start with Momirya.
I'd like you to take a look.
Here's Momirinya's crush outfit!
I have an image.
I have an image
I'd like you to see it.
Here's Mirinya's crush outfit
This outfit...
Oh, my God.
I, Mirinya, listen to me. Maybe it's imprinted on you in the middle of the sound.
But I have an image of Mirinya as "Ong-Chu-Ong-Chu-Ong-Chu".
It's amazing.
I really like the sound inside the sound, and I like my own shape the best.
I'm so happy to hear from fans that they like Milinha in Oto-Chu Oto-Chu as well.
It was everyone's favorite.
Next up is Hana-chan.
Here is Hana-chan's Kimetee Award!
Oh!
Go for it!
I know!
I understand!
Let's go for it!
Yes, sir!
Boo-boo, you're really hurting me, you're really hurting me.
Patty, you're a real gal!
In my time, when gal was in her prime, there was one girl in my class who had a really good personality and took good care of us.
She's a very caring person who makes things fun...
Her brightness, her slickness... everything was exactly as I'd imagined.
That's why I like your fitting.
But this one's already out of the design...
The first thing that you need to do is to get a good look at the design of the shoes.
I've got a request for a light blue ningam check.
I wanted to make it in a light blue ningam check, but I wanted it to have a little point.
So I added some bluish pink.
The decorations are also a little bit clear.
It's filled with all the things Riasai likes.
I love the design with the fluffy shoulders.
It looks good on her.
Also, I think it looks really good with her belly showing a little.
Sashiara-san gave me the haircut when we were doing "Natsu no Tope" and I wore it for the first time for the title song.
I remember the first time I wore a half-twin hairstyle for the title song.
Half-twins are so cute!
It looks good on me.
Cute is really cute
Sweet, sweet, sweet.
It's really a little print
The gravure is so cute!
It's so cute! It'd be a shame to show it off. Everyone should buy one.
It's so cute. It's really, really good.
Next up is Kiara. Here's Kiara's crush show.
She's got pink hair and she looks like an American high school girl.
She really looks like a foreign girl. She's so cute.
I'm so happy.
I love this one so much.
It's so cute!
There aren't many casual types like this.
I was thinking that one day I'd like to make an American casual outfit for Chiara like this.
I'd love to make an outfit for Chiara like this.
Wow!
I'm so happy!
Next is Maika!
Here's Maika's crush outfit!
Surprisingly, maybe.
Oh!
I know!
I can see it.
Mayka, you know, like Zulu and that girl...
She looks good with that kind of thing.
But there are two things I like about Mayka.
Maica in the rain and Maica when she's angry.
Once a year, you know...
Only once a year, at the Icono Joy Festival, we get wet in the rain.
Oh, a scene like that.
Right.
And you can see Micah getting wet in the rain.
But, you know, only when it's like this, I don't know what it is...
I can see angry mica, mica with an angry face.
That's right.
Yeah...
His mushed face is really beautiful, beautiful, beautiful!
Also, I can't hear the instructions, when they're being given in the earpiece, or in rehearsal.
I can't hear you.
I love it!
Oh my god! Oh, my God!
I also make a face like that.
Shinobu-san has always said that she likes my angry face, so I'm a little confused.
But I like this song and this outfit, and I like kimono-style kimonos, so I thought I looked good in kimonos too.
I think I look good in kimonos. I think I look good in Japanese style.
I love this outfit!
I hope you all get mad from the factory when I show it off.
Oh no!
Visual check!
They're going to do a visual check.
I have to see the visual check.
I'm going to get angry.
Let's move on to the next member. Hitomi is next.
Here's Hitomi's crush outfit!
I wonder...
Oh!
Oh, I see it!
This is it!
Hitomi's been getting a lot of buzz for this outfit!
I love this part of Hitomi's dress.
The American sleeves on the shoulders... these things really pick the right person.
I've been working on idol costumes for many years, and there are only a few people who look good in them.
That shape looks good on me.
And the shoulder line from the collarbone is so beautiful.
All I can do is show off my smile.
She's embarrassed.
She's so cute.
It's amazing.
You know, I tend to do this a lot... because it's me.
No, he says I'm overdoing it with this look.
Yes!
You're right, it's amazing.
There are a lot of peacel shapes.
Hitomi's Peacel outfit is done here, too.
Yes, yes, it looks good on you.
But it's the 6th anniversary, so I think it's a good choice.
It looks good on you.
You've been really polished lately.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I thought Hitomi was beautiful when she came in when I was in school.
LOL.
That's right.
Yes, I thought she was beautiful.
Thank you very much.
I'm a little embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed.
You're hot!
It's hot.
Hot?
Okay, next is Shoko.
Here's Shoko in her crush outfit.
Oh, wow!
I know, I know
Pants look good on you
They look great on you!
I couldn't find anything to fix when I put it on for the fitting.
Shoko changed pretty early in the fitting.
I was already thinking of Shoko as a role model.
Aaaaah!
I thought Shoko's look was the right one.
And then I started fitting everyone like this.
But pants look great on her.
Japanese people like skirts a lot.
I like skirts.
I like skirts because I usually wear hair extensions.
I see.
Yes, I do a lot of hair removal and wear plain clothes.
That's right.
It looks great on you.
I love this outfit.
The body conscious part
and the body of the pants
I thought it was a winner at the fitting.
I couldn't fix it and I thought, "I'm just going to go with it.
It looked great on me, so I went with it.
Yay! Great next time!
Next up is Iori.
Here's Iori's "crush" outfit.
Kipi.
You're right!
Including I-chan's hair at this time.
And her twintails...
Iori Noguchi is a cool guy...
But she's still a baby, isn't she?
I think I was able to express the cute Iori in just the right amount.
But I also want to add a bit of hardness from the neck up.
It's very Iori-like.
When I received this song for the first time
I was worried about whether I'd look good in this kind of costume.
But when I saw the outfit
When I saw it...
What? A little sweet and spicy?
Yes.
I could tell that you thought a lot about making a costume that was uniquely me.
It's my favorite costume.
I'm so happy.
I miss it so much!
I made a good pun on the pork bone.
Ahhh...
You don't have to.
What? You don't have to?
I don't have to.
I'm glad I didn't.
Foreshadowing.
And Sanatun.
Here's Sanatun's crush outfit.
Oh!
Foreshadowing recovery
Foreshadowing recovery foreshadowing recovery foreshadowing recovery
Really.
This really fits so well.
Foreshadowing!
When Sanatun sings, she turns her head to the side...
You know...
You sing like you're floating in the air.
I really change my right hand to the microphone when I sing.
I change it.
Change it
Change, change, change
I like to sing with my left hand, so I sing with my left hand.
I see.
It's like I'm really happy.
Like I'm alive because I'm drinking beer.
I'm going to sing it.
It's good when you can sing quietly because it's dressy, but it's also good
but when she sings a cool, hard song in a cool way...
Sanatun is my favorite singer.
Please give it a try!
I think she really pulls out the best in the column, and she does a great job with this outfit.
I've been working on it since the moment we had the fitting.
Why did you do Isshin Denshin?
I thought this was it.
Hey, you're being mischievous.
And last but not least, here's my crush's costume.
Here's my crush's costume.
It's a costume from your favorite 48 group.
It's a costume from one of your favorite 48 groups, but it has three of the four patterns.
I didn't design it for you, but it fits you perfectly.
You like this corset, don't you?
At the fitting, I said, "This looks really good on you.
I told her she should wear it.
Yes, you did wear it.
She also displayed it at the costume show.
I thought it looked really good on you.
The shirt looks good on you, too.
I like the way the shirt fits me.
I like the collar, so I'm glad.
The petite figure is cute, and it also makes you look a little cool.
It's like An-chan.
I'm happy.
But I haven't been able to wear it lately.
I want to wear it.
I want to.
You've grown up a bit, haven't you?
I'm sure Nia Joy and the others will wear it in a year or so.
That's for sure.
I'll wear it.
You're giving it to Nia Joy.
No, you can't.
I'm not giving you that.
That's not for you.
Our costumes.
People are pretty hungry for them. No, no.
They said it was important. They've all left.
I see.
Thank you.
You wore An-chan's costume.
She wore An-chan's costume
You wore An-chan's costume
By the way, it's almost time for the Issehon Jyuhanki Special Live!
So how was your day, Kaka-chan?
Today was the first time for me to talk with Shinano-san.
We've talked a lot with Shinano-san today... and we've gone from having a nice talk to expressing our deepest thoughts and feelings.
I could feel the deep feelings you have deep inside.
It made me happy.
I had a meaningful time with you, didn't I?
I hope you had a meaningful time.
I'm going to fry up some eggs!
Thank you very much for your wonderful comment!
That was Risato.
I didn't expect you to reject me.
I was caught off guard, but I'm so happy to have been asked to be in the costume book.
I'm so happy to have been able to publish a costume book like this, but I'm also very happy to have been able to do it.
I'm so happy to have been asked to do a costume book like this, but...
Ten and a half.
Ten and a half
ten and a half
10.5
10 and a half
ten and a half
awesome
oh
to
ap
We love Shinobe-san so much.
We were so happy to be able to talk with you like this.
We also realized that you love us so much.
We are so happy to know that you love us so much and
I'm so happy!
LOL!
It's so good.
This is
I'm so happy!
I'm really happy!
I knew it... I mean, various idol girls and stuff.
I've heard that the costumes from Equal Love
They said how cute the costumes were.
I'm glad that people are looking at our costumes
I'm really happy that people are looking at our costumes.
I think the live performance is great.
The live performance is great, so I hope you all enjoy the tour.
The arena tour is about to start.
I'm looking forward to it.
We're still working on the costumes for the arena tour.
I don't know.
We're just getting fitted now.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it!
So, once again, thank you so much for taking time out of your busy schedule
Thank you very much for coming today, Shinobu-san!
It was a lot of fun.
It was a lot of fun!
I hope that Equal will continue to make wonderful costumes for everyone
I would like to do my best more and more so that we can make wonderful costumes together.
Thank you very much for your support!
Thank you very much.
See you again then!
Bye bye!